♪ In the
not-too-distant future ♪
♪ Way down in Deep 13 ♪
♪ The evil Dr. Forrester ♪
♪ Was hatchin' a nasty scheme ♪
♪ He hired a temp by
the name of Mike ♪
♪ Just a regular
joe he didn't like ♪
♪ His experiment needed
a good test case ♪
♪ So he conked him on the noggin
and he shot him into space ♪
- [Mike] Get me down
♪ I'll send him cheesy movies ♪
♪ Ooh ooh ooh ♪
♪ The worst I can find ♪
♪ La la la ♪
♪ He'll have to sit
and watch them all ♪
♪ And I'll monitor his mind ♪
♪ La la la ♪
♪ Now keep in mind
Mike can't control ♪
♪ When the movies begin or end ♪
♪ La la la ♪
♪ He'll try to keep his sanity ♪
♪ With the help of
his robot friends ♪
♪ Robot Roll Call ♪
♪ Cambot ♪
♪ Cover yourself ♪
♪ Gypsy ♪
♪ I'm not ready ♪
♪ Tom Servo ♪
♪ Hello there ♪
♪ Crooooow ♪
♪ That's one o ♪
♪ If you're wondering how
he eats and breathes ♪
♪ And other science facts ♪
♪ La la la ♪
♪ Just repeat to yourself
it's just a show ♪
♪ I should really just relax ♪
- Did I tell you
my mother's here?
♪ For Mystery Science
Theater 3000 ♪
(whirring and clanking)
(Mike mumbling)
- Hello there!
(chuckling) Welcome to the SOL,
the Satellite of Laughs
as we like to call it.
- (chuckling) We've tied up Mike
and jammed an oily
rag into his mouth
so that we may bring
you the following joke.
(Mike screaming)
- You see, if you live long
enough, eventually someone's
going to say the word
thunderdome in your presence.
- That's right and I'm
guessin' most of you
aren't equipped with
a snappy comeback.
Well, we're gonna give ya one!
(both chuckling)
- We'll act it out for you.
Boy, I still think
we really screwed up
on that whole
Thunderdome fiasco.
- Oh, come on, can't we
just get beyond thunderdome?
(both laughing)
Thank you!
- Thank you, thank you!
Now, as you can see, your
stooge can't mention the movie
Beyond Thunderdome 'cause that
just ruins the whole joke.
You'll just have to wait
until someone mentions
a thunderdome, not the specific
one in Beyond Thunderdome.
(Mike mumbling)
- Also, it really helps
if your stooge speaks
of a thunderdome in
a disparaging manner,
as in our little playlet.
It'll still work if he
speaks of a thunderdome
in a positive light,
but if I were you,
I'd wait until somebody
slams a thunderdome.
(both laughing)
Now, let's move on to
the rangoon version
of this classic joke.
- Oh, yes!
(Mike screaming)
(upbeat music)
(Crow laughing)
- Yeah, real funny,
you guys finished yet?
- Oh sure!
- Yeah, why?
- Well, usually
your little riffs
tend to go on and
on maybe a little...
- Oh please, Mike, can't
we get beyond the riff?
(both laughing)
- Oh, that's it, go to
your room, both of you!
- Huh?
- Hey!
The booth died.
- What's goin' on?
- What?
Oh, are you still there?
Oh, that's right, I forgot
to disconnect the umbilicus!
Look out, Mother!
- Oh, that might...
- We can see where the...
- [All] Huh?
- Cut the umbili, why?
- You can't disconnect
the umbilicus!
- We'll die!
- Oh, nonsense,
you'll be pulled into
Earth's gravitational field,
your orbit will decay,
the hull will rupture,
you'll burn to a crisp,
and then you'll die!
(hissing)
- What?
You, you can't do that,
we've done everything
you've ever asked,
we watched every bad
movie you sent up here!
- [Servo And Crow] Yeah!
- Sorry, buh-bye!
- But you said you'd let
us get back to Earth!
- Did I say that?
Hmm, well, maybe I did.
What do you want?
I'm evil!
- Well, this is kinda sudden.
- Look, I'm really very
sorry, my hands are tied!
I got a letter today,
my funding has been cut,
and you guys just aren't
cutting the mustard so...
- Well, I'm gonna make
another trip over,
I think I found Frank.
- Oh, no, mother, that's
Frank's spare head,
why don't we just
put that in storage?
- Got it.
- (sighing) I'm moving back in
with Mom to save some scratch.
At least her
building has a pool.
I'm sorry, what was the problem?
- How can you do this to us?
- Aw, criminy, I got an idea.
- Wh, wh, what are we
supposed to do now?
- I don't know, do
what you always do.
Look, I've gotta fill out
these change of address cards.
- Well, I'm gonna take
another load over.
Back in a few.
Boy, I'm glad I never
got rid of the big rig.
- Anyway, guys, your
orbit will begin to decay
in about two hours
so I've downloaded
a film from the ship's
internal memory.
It's called Laserblast
and Leonard Maltin
gives it two-and-a-half stars!
(whirring)
- Now what?
- Thruster engines firing,
we now have impulse power!
- Well, how did you do that?
- I took the cover off!
- We have helm, Captain!
- Now entering
Earth's atmosphere,
hull temperature critical!
- Do we have enough power
to escape the atmosphere?
- Ach, we won't have control,
we'll be shot into deep space,
I've got to have more time!
- We don't have that time!
Get ready to engage
warp engines, Mr. Crow.
- Aye-aye.
- Engage.
(alarm blaring)
- Oh, we got movies sign!
- Movie sign!
- [Mike] I didn't engage
the thing with you!
(whirring and clanking)
(Tom Servo humming)
- Look at this, a Famuel
Goldwyn production.
- Ooh.
- I had an infection of
the Yablans one time.
- Ah, the Charlie Daniels
Band is now the Charles Band.
If you ever go down
to the wooley swamp.
- Terrible name for
laser eye surgery,
scares away the customers.
- Come on down to Milford,
free popsicles for the kids.
(ominous music)
So, what, they just had people
from data entry to
be in this movie?
- Gianni Russo, I remember
her from, uh, wait a minute...
- The Keenan Wynn
comes blowin' in!
- You are the Wynn
beneath my Keenan.
- Oh, isn't he
the guy who, no...
♪ Barry Cutler ♪
♪ Ron Masak ♪
- Brother of Bob, Mike Enko.
- Ugh.
- Ah,
so you know it won't be funny.
- Heir to the Arnold
Stang fortune.
- As Dr. Casaba Melon.
- Brother of Neill, Steve Enko!
- I saw a Wolman drinkin' a
pina colada at Trader Vic's.
- Wow, Roddy McDowall
and Dave Allen!
- No for them to tell me all
this, I'm no good at names.
- Whoa, is he an American band?
I hope he comes to our town
and helps us party it down.
- These credits give you a
chance to finish your popcorn,
talk a little, decide
to see another movie.
- The music has a decidedly
Hawkwind feel to it.
- I think it's more of a, like,
Mike Oldfield-McHenry
Spring-Rick
Wakeman-Jean-Michel JaRae
- Keith Emerson-Gentle
Giant-Tomeda Autobahn
Craft Synergy
sort of thing.
- I certainly hope
we see how credits
at the end of the movie, too.
- And, action!
Cut!
Beautiful.
- These plains were once filled
with wild broccoli like this.
- Fievel Goes West.
- Looks like Trent Reznor
ran out of gas, poor guy!
- It was after the Acropolis.
- Roxy!
- Somebody please pull this
garbage disposal off my arm!
- Ah, Robert Smith is
in a good mood today!
- Edward CDplayerhand.
- Boy, the Hulk has lost weight.
- Remember when
he was over there?
That was a good
part of the movie.
(wind blowing)
- Man, if we could just get
some butter to slip in there,
try to slide this thing off.
- Well, back to
whatever I was doing.
- Hm?
Norelco's plan for
world domination!
- Even its name spells
Merry Christmas!
- I'm hunting spacecwaft
(goofy laughing).
- We wish to welcome
you to Denver's airport.
(whirring)
- Oh great, ET calls, we
come, and he's not here.
- Hey, Yertle, you left
your shell in the ship!
(alien speaking alien language)
- Hey.
Hey, Wally, come out here,
help me find Roswell.
(alien speaking alien language)
Hey, you got my shirt
all stretched out.
- I told you to ask directions
at the Gorlon Station
at Zing-Ding Five but no,
you blabzeemed ahead of
that guy on Bartoole!
(beeping)
- Just past this football.
- Stop reading my thoughts,
are you reading my thoughts?
- Look out, it's Gino Vannelli!
(whooshing)
- Tonight on a very
special Virginian.
(zapping)
- Good shooting, Zanthar.
- Thanks, Denise.
- Ah, Christina's World 3001.
- Help me, Spock.
Spock!
- I know what you're thinking,
did I fire six
gorlocks or only five?
- Okay, Crow, that's enough.
(whirring)
- (gasping) The key
to the Amaco bathroom!
- Am I good, huh?
Who's the king! (laughing)
(plane humming)
- Look out, ET!
- Boy, I love airplanes,
is that a Cessna?
- No, I think it was a Piper.
Nah, let's get outta here.
- Huh, might've used a little
too much buckshot here,
ruined the meat.
♪ Closer shave cleaner
shave smoother all the way ♪
- Help, a giant bong
is attacking me, oh!
- Mike, this is how I've
always pictured your room,
am I far off?
- (chuckling) Well...
Well, off the
weight loss clinic.
- Ah, get 'em off me, get 'em
off, oh, it's just my sheets.
- Hm, somehow his mustardy
shorts don't help.
- These are relatively
clean, I guess.
- Ojai, crap, I'm still in Ojai!
- Randy Johnson?
Oh, it's a her.
- So, here's my Slimfast,
Metrecal, Correctol.
- Excuse me, are you my mother?
- Here is her food
supply for the month,
in that train case right there.
- Flesh is a nice
color for a house.
(all groaning)
- Shawn Cassidy in Walking Tall.
- Where you headed, tubbo?
Stay and have Quisp with
me at the junky table.
(Tom Servo and Crow screaming)
- She's one of
the turtle aliens!
- I'm sorry I called you fat.
- Come on, let's pop
anals and watch Days.
- Man, if those pants blow,
it's gonna be like
a piano exploding.
- I've got this invitation
to go to Acapulco.
- Well, that bounced
off his head.
- Well, it's just
too good to miss!
- And you got your James
Spader lessons and...
- Well, my chemical peel
is starting to hurt,
I better get going.
- What do you want?
- Mama, you've been to Acapulco.
How many times you
wanna go to Acapulco?
- 'Til they stop
asking me, sweetheart!
- And until I stop killing
men with my hipbones!
Oh, I hate you!
- There's a box a Weetabix,
that should last you the month.
- I'm gonna go untie the
Nazi helmet from the roof.
- Is this Underall
aversion therapy?
- You can actually
see her lose weight!
- Huh?
Ah, now onto movie three.
- Hey, kung fu got a van!
- Another slice of your
life here, Mike, huh?
Just you ribbin' a highway,
your Dixie Dregs
tapes (chuckling).
♪ Well I'm the friendly
stranger in the black sedan ♪
- He's so happy his
dingleball shipment came in.
- Oh, Bernie Preston
takes a solo.
- Whoa, 70s Gold
was a great buy,
a lot of good stuff on here!
- I'll warrant that van
is still on the road.
- Hi, Gary.
Hi, Jason.
Hey, Scotty.
- Ah, Downtown Hugo.
Well, I'm pretty sure
this is the long version
of whatever the
heck song this is.
- I'm gonna go around the
block until the song's over.
- This guy killed
himself when the
Edgar Winter Group broke up.
- This guy has put more rolled
up towels under more doors.
- Man, this is one of the most
innovative synth
players I know of.
- Mm-hmm, yep, it's a sunny day,
you got a pleasant
buzz goin', hey, Mike?
Huh, huh?
- Yeah, yeah.
- I gotta stop and listen
to this part, it's so cool.
- Hey, his van's got a
poop catcher on the back.
- Hmm!
Wow, and you thought
Willie Aames was hot, hoo!
- Yeah, I did.
- Jeez, stupid realtor job,
I gotta wear a shirt just
to show a dumb house.
(upbeat music)
- Hey, Spicer, I'm
here for the dope.
- Go.
- It's me, Billy!
- He woke up Ram Dass!
- Password.
- It's me, Colonel, Billy
Duncan, I just wanna see Kathy.
- Buy you own paper!
- You get off these premises.
- Aw, come on, Colonel,
I only wanna see Kathy!
- What about?
- I wanna see if Electra
tore up her new shoes!
- Well, that's private.
- That's private.
- It's Yukon Cornelius.
- What is this stuff
you're pulling on me?
You're just like those guys,
those white collar guys
down there at Cherry Point!
- Keenan started early today.
- Everything is hush-hush!
- Sweet Charlotte!
- Operation: Sand
Dust, hush-hush!
- Sweet Charlotte!
- Everybody connected
with it, hush-hush!
- Sweet Charlotte!
- Everybody except me,
because I know something
they didn't know I knew!
Now you get away from that!
- Hey look, just 'cause that
mine went off in your helmet...
- You bastards are all alike!
With your disguises and
your tricks and your...
- Hula hoops!
- Colonel, if you'd
just call Kathy.
- Now you leave Kathy outta
this, you leave, you leave...
- Oh, gee, what's her name?
I just said it, uh, um...
- Oh, ever since
the Colonel got back
from the Spanish-American War.
- I know, I'll seek refuge
in 20 explosive hits
by 20 explosive stars!
- Operation: Sand Dust.
- Grandpa?
- Anna Nicole Smith
and her husband.
- Operation: Sand Dust.
♪ Old black water
keep on rollin' ♪
♪ Mississippi moon
won't you keep on ♪
- Was that Billy?
- Come on, your pork
backs are ready.
- Grandpa!
- Snap out of it,
you old bastard!
- Grandpa, come on inside.
- Why'd you open all the
cans of soup, Grandpa?
- The army have the Potomac
has us on the run,
sweetie, yeah.
(energetic music)
- His 8-track's about
to change tracks.
Ca-chunk, ca-chunk.
- Oh yeah, you do a lot
of wacky tabacky, Mike?
Lot of Mary Jane, perhaps?
Jokey Smokey?
- (sighing) What do you
keep smoking that stuff for?
- Starksky and Hutch have been
together a little too long!
- Don't cost nothin'.
I take her from those kids.
- You keep smokin' that,
you're gonna get us
thrown off the force.
- Look, are you ready
for some football?
- You ever notice how
Haile Selassie is God?
- Now you're gettin'
horny, great!
- Hey, that feels
good (chuckling).
- Aw, give me a puff!
(police radio chattering)
- Then I gotta go home and
get ready for some football!
- You know, now
that I think of it,
Sister Mary Elephant
is really funny!
- Well, they targeted this
movie to lonely bass fishermen.
- In other words,
- [All] Bass fishermen.
- Whoa!
- Who was that?
- I think it's that Bill Duncan.
- That Duncan kid, huh?
Well, let's go get him.
- Let's find out if he's
ready for some football!
(engine revving)
(tires squealing)
- Ah, the famous squealing
tires on a dirt road.
- You idiot!
- I'm a dumb, scrawny cracker!
- They're at least as
funny as Cheech and Chong.
- Oh, definitely.
(police siren wailing)
Ron Howard pops the clutch,
signals, checks both ways,
and proceeds gently
into traffic,
politely inviting
people to eat his dust!
- He looks like a bush baby!
- I'm gonna push it up to 17!
- My heart is in my throat!
Oh wait, that's not
my heart (coughing).
- Pull over, squeal like a pig!
- All right, force him over!
- And quit scannin' me!
- Whoa, my horse knuckle
breakfast almost came up!
- You know, Mike,
it's hard not to make
a Dukes of Hazzard comment.
- Try, honey.
- I will.
♪ Show me the way to
the next whiskey bar ♪
(goofy music)
Suddenly I long for
a Hal Needham film.
- Yeah, what do we got?
Another citizen who isn't
ready for some football?
(Tom Servo and Crow making
stomping sound effects)
Nice hinder, hm.
- Wow, that's not a very
good detail painting.
- You never learn, do you, boy?
- Hey, can't you let
me go just this once?
I'm gonna blow my insurance,
I'm already payin' double!
- Yeah, that's all right,
your mama's got enough money.
- Kinda heavyset,
though, ain't she?
- By the way, how is
your mama these days?
- I think I resent
your attitude.
- Nevermind, just give me
the ticket, Officer Ungar.
- Sign there boy,
I'll make you a star.
- Oh eat me, you
fuzzy marshmallow.
- Hey, you know cursive!
- Your ticket for
going 20 in a 30.
- Well, if you'll excuse me,
there's a bag of Mama
Burgers waitin' for me.
- Oh man, it's
uphill to the car,
I don't know if I can make it.
- You could put your entire
head in his bellybutton.
(engine revving)
- Do we get him again, Pete?
- (sighing) Nah, too damn hot.
- Anyway, all my rowdy
friends are coming over later.
Honk, honk, hoooonk!
(engine revving)
- Dirty and hairy.
- When you first saw
this, you laughed so hard
you spilled your bong
water, didn't you, Mike?
- Galahad, no!
- Oh, those lovable Southern
California crackers.
- Hi, I'm Max Keller!
- He should rub salt
on those leeches
on the side of his van.
- Well, I better stock up on
Ollie Joe Prater and
Jerry Clower tapes.
- He's gonna get
a new baseball cap
with a fake dog turd on it.
(bell ringing)
- Hey, it's that gas station
that Frank Lloyd
Wright didn't design.
- Wow, if there was ignorant
talk radio in the 70s,
I sure would agree with it.
- Are those bootcut
jeans for Moon Boots?
- Karen Carpenter's phone booth.
- Okay, I'll give you your
Coke, stop hittin' me!
- I'm gonna drink the
hell out of this Coke.
- Coca Cola's gonna
need a PR campaign
just to undo the damage
this scene is doin'.
- Oh man, Leif Garrett did
more harm than he'll ever know.
- Well, Merry
Christmas everybody.
(horn honking)
- Hey, you wouldn't believe
what just happened
at Dealey Plaza!
- Oh, he teases the
gas pumps mercilessly!
- Well, let's recap
the movie so far.
Somebody went to Acapulco and
somebody almost bought gas.
(Chuck and Froggy yelling)
- Just when I was considering
not committing suicide,
it has finally come
together for me.
- The accelerator
pedal's stuck, help us!
(horn honking)
- Hey, you wanna go drive
around gas stations with us?
- You see who's out early
this mornin', Froggy?
- I bet he ain't got
our reason, Chuck!
- No, he wouldn't like that
kinda party, it's a little
too rough for him.
- He's Deezen!
- I've been up all night
and I don't feel sleepy.
Hey, Froggy, you
think our boy here
would like to give
us a little race?
- Billy?
Hell, he never races!
- Who the hell told you that?
I'll show you a race!
- Just let me get into my
dad's electric supply van!
- Inverted world
where the spazzes
make fun of the cool guys.
(engine sputtering)
(Chuck and Froggy laughing)
- Steven Stills and Bill Gates!
- [Froggy] Oh, right, how
much handicap you want?
- Ah, the Sinclair
station is open,
they got an air hose! (laughing)
- Makes me glad rural
America is dying.
♪ Ah-ha ha ha wipeout! ♪
(whirring and clanking)
- Oh, get away from
me, you little creep!
- I will not get away,
I have been sent here to
destroy imperfections,
I find you, the gold
unit, to be imperfect!
- Yeah?
Well smooch my tiny,
imperfect little...
- Well, hey, loser, what it is?
- Ah, I got one of these
Nomad satellites on my butt.
Seems you can't go hurtling
into the void of space
without picking up one of these
annoying little busybodies!
- You are in error,
I am not Nomad,
I'm a similar design
known as Monad.
- Monad?
I should destroy you
but I'll give you a
mulligan on that one.
(Mike and Tom Servo laughing)
What, what?
Did you say something imperfect?
- No, no, I'm sorry,
go on with your story.
- Stop it, cut it out!
Look, if you're going to
say something imperfect,
say it to the group!
- Oh, no, it's just that I was
tellin' these guys, you know,
we're having a little
party on Thursday night,
little pop and pizza, wondered
if you'd like to join us.
- Sure, that sounds great!
- Ha, the party's on
Friday night, not Thursday!
That means you're
wrong and imperfect
and you have to
destroy yourself.
- You told me a fib, that
doesn't mean I'm imperfect.
- Does too!
- Yeah, it does.
- Does not!
- Does too!
If you were perfect,
you would've known
he was tellin' a fib.
- Look, I'm not going to get
into this with you clowns,
you're imperfect
and I'm just going
to destroy the lot of you.
- Yeah, right, whatever.
- Oh, I'm so scared!
Give me your worst, come
on you big, dumb can!
(Monad yelling)
Come on, do it, do it!
- Come on, dummy,
let's get you out.
- Get out into space
you dumb robot!
- Yeah, baby, so stupid!
- We'll be right back.
- Oh, fun!
(upbeat music)
(all laughing)
♪ Lady ♪
♪ When you're with
me I'm smilin' ♪
- Okay, thanks.
♪ Whoa whoa whoa whoa ♪
- Good thing my
frosted tip took!
- Pepsi gave 'em big bucks
to place Coke in this movie.
- Ah, the Navajos get
all the good land.
- Lyle Swann's motorcycle
from Timerider!
- I'll just pull up here
so I can find this thing
and then we can get
the movie goin'.
(high-pitched tone)
- I really am just dust in the
wind, man, they are so right.
- Yeah, on his day off
from pizza delivery,
he sure knows how to live life.
- I'd like to call
my horse with no name
but it doesn't have a name.
- Good God, he's out of Coke!
(booming)
- Uh, Billy, go to expression B.
- Funky Winkerbean!
- This is just like the
beginning of the film,
where it may or may
not have been my dream!
- Aw, where's its mom?
- Wow, Albert Belle
did cork his bat!
- Oh, this is so great, I
needed hooker headers bad!
- Dun
Duh-duh!
- Think of all the dope
I could smoke with this.
- Man, to think I was depressed
when Battlestar
Galactica got canceled!
- Can't we just visit
Mom in Acapulco?
- Duh-duh!
- Okay.
- Sorry.
- Does he always waltz around
when he finds old
Thorin's tone arms?
- I hope he's pointing
it at his heart.
- Duh-duh!
Someone threw away a
perfectly good arm remover.
Duh-duh-duh, duh!
- A Daisy Red Rider
repeating rifle, thanks, Dad!
- Now, let's go
find some ptarmigan!
- Pah-pah-pow!
- After all that,
it's pah-pah-pow.
- Once you're over the age of
11, you should not say pow.
- Pah-pow, pow!
- Please, stop, stop it
- Come on.
- Please, no, no, no.
- I think he's doin'
Frampton Comes Alive.
- That's even worse.
- So, it's a thing
that makes you waltz.
- I guess.
- Won't he be surprised
when he finds out
it doesn't go pow but swish!
- Oh, found it.
Now he has carte blanche
to the Amaco men's room!
(tense music)
- Bloopidy-bloo-bloo.
(zapping)
(Crow imitating
monkey shrieking)
- Hopefully that thing has a
shirt buttoning attachment.
- Pow?
- Do the apes know they're
filming in the Forbidden Zone?
- Ah!
One of Mr. T's
understated pieces.
- You know those apes who stack
boxes to get to the bananas
figure things out a
lot faster than this.
(whooshing)
(booming)
(dramatic music)
Yeah, I think you are gonna
detail my van for $75!
Huh, what's that?
You want me to go to gym class?
I don't think so!
I think I'll have that leather
vest my friend (chuckling).
- Mm-hmm!
By the way, we seem to be
involved in laserblasting now.
- Right!
(whooshing)
(booming)
Moses!
- Yes, Yahweh in a can.
If you wanna summon
Yahweh (chuckling).
(whooshing)
(booming)
- Uh, you might wanna
calibrate your iron sights,
it's kinda pullin'
to the right there.
(Mike laughing goofily)
(whooshing)
(booming)
- That's okay, just a
2000-year-old saguaro,
don't worry about it.
(Crow imitating
monkey shrieking)
(Tom Servo spitting)
- It's Georgia O'Keeffe's
massive limousine.
- Ah, your film crew,
ladies and gentlemen!
- Oh, want a Dick Butkus mug?
A little orange ball
for your aerial?
Hello?
- The Bill Bixby line of
David Bernie clothing.
- Excuse me, I just got
crabs from your toilet.
- Oh, look at all the 8-tracks.
Frannie and Teicher,
Captain and Tennille.
(man screaming)
- (gasping) Warren,
I, oh, it's you.
- What do I owe you?
- Uh...
That'll be, uh...
- Let's see, five bucks
for the butt nudge and...
- Uh, sorry, I didn't
hear you comin',
that'll be $11.15 with the oil.
- Here's my Merle Haggard
Visa, I assume you take that.
- Oh, my new club magazine,
I should wait until I
get to the hotel but...
- Thank you, Mr. Craig.
- I threw in a nudie
calender for free.
- How far is it to
the nearest hotel?
- You stopping here?
- I could be persuaded.
- You don't like
this town, buddy?
- Oh, sure, sure!
It's just a few blocks to the
end of town there's a hotel.
- Or there's the Ziffo
BnB, that's nice.
You could go down, oh, sorry.
- So he just drove off
and I never saw him again,
the beautiful sweet man in the
Palm Beach suit (sniffling).
Just drove outta my life.
- She's floating!
♪ Get my motor running ♪
♪ Head out on the highway ♪
♪ Do do do do do do do ♪
Oh, pretty steep grade here!
Oh!
- I'm in the weeds
here (chuckling).
- I know she's there, don't
lose her, hold on, don't, ah!
- There she is!
- The air feels nice when I
ride like this, hee hee hee.
Hee.
- Hee.
- Billy told me he'd meet me
at the old creosote dump site.
- Wow, the county
really provides
good service at
those picnic sites!
Look, a bottle of
Beaujolais and...
- Billy?
- I'd like to buy
some sweet corn!
- Billy!
- Or I'd like to
buy a Turkish rug?
- Did they need to
come to Angkor Wat
just to have a picnic?
- (humming) Well,
I might as well
pray to Vaal while I'm here.
- Yep.
Well.
- Hey, say Billy again,
that'll liven things up!
- Yeah, maybe I'll
pick up a dozen
sucker minnows while I'm here.
- (humming) Oh, well, he
hasn't been cremated, ha ha.
(Tom Servo and Mike humming)
- Oh, did my parents burn
down the house and move away?
- So we're watching someone
waiting for someone.
- Yeah, yep, mm-hmm.
- There's a point where
to stops being a movie.
- It's like watching
an aquarium!
- Yep.
- This is so something.
- Suddenly that scene
out in the desert
seems taut and well-executed.
(Billy roaring)
(Kathy yelping)
- Oh, you keep this
relationship fresh!
- See, now that scene worked
'cause you expected
a bear to jump out.
- Oh, you're more trouble
than you're worth.
- Am I?
Am I?
- I'll kill you for saying
that, I'll kill you, I tell you!
- Ow, ow, there's a
folding shovel in there!
- Well, if you don't look like
the cat that
swallowed the cream.
Where've you been all morning?
- Geez, her bra looks
like a pair of sunglasses!
- Not waking people up at
the crack of dawn, I hope.
- Oh, that's where they
found Tony Orlando.
- Psh, Crow!
- Can't you be more ordinary?
- More ordinary?
Man, he'd have to work at that.
(gentle music)
- Grandpa's so mad right now.
He says he's gonna
shoot you on sight
next time you set
foot on the property.
- Wow, we have
someone to root for!
- I do believe if you were
more ordinary, though,
you wouldn't be my
Billy, would you?
(Tom Servo snoring)
It's so peaceful here.
I wish it was always this way.
- Oh, mm-hmm.
- Just you and me and the sky.
- A dog named Boo.
- [Kathy] A giant blue cup.
- Yeah.
- Yeah, look, can we
start mashin' now?
- And we're the
dregs, poured out.
- Just what I wanna see,
David Soul and Sandra
Locke goin' at it.
- There's somethin' so
dark in you sometimes.
Just sends shivers
up and down my spine.
- Like when you crank
Don't Fear the Reaper.
- Oh, geez, nature
videos of big spiders
goin' at it are more appealing.
- Are you crazy?
You wanna be late?
- [Billy] For what?
- For Franny's birthday party,
we're all due there about three.
- Yeah, I don't
wanna go to no party.
- Come on, I'm cookin' a
pizza on the engine block!
- Well, Mr. Billy Duncan,
if you don't wanna go,
I could always
accept an invitation
by a certain Chuck Boran.
- Over my dead body.
- Yes!
- Please, please, please!
- What's this?
- I think it's the stermin,
does that sound right?
- I don't know.
Could be somethin'
bit me when I was...
- When you was what?
- I was fooling around in
the desert this morning.
- The desert gave you a hickey?
- You better put something on
that, it looks pretty mean.
- He died.
(upbeat music)
(buzzing)
- Meanwhile on Quark.
Remember Quark?
- Yeah, I loved it.
- I'm thinking of getting
an ass reduction, Ted.
- You ever just curse evolution?
(beeping)
- Every store named
RadioShack is just crap!
- Adjust the cone filter here.
- So this is DSS, huh?
- Howdy-doo!
- Hey, read between the lines.
- Uh, your move,
sir, you called us.
(alien speaking alien language)
- Don't start.
Well, did you?
Oh, please, sir,
we've seen Laserblast.
- This is how advanced
the aliens are,
they can edit this scene down.
- Boy, when a movie starts
showing you parts of itself,
you know you're in trouble.
- Look what the hairy
no-butt is doing, the fool!
- Their puny human butt pods
fell off thousands of years ago!
(sighing) Okay.
Uh, thank you, sir, I think
we get the gist of it!
Uh, is there a point to
your little call, sir?
Sir?
(alien speaking alien language)
- You get out there
and sell, sell, sell!
(aliens speaking alien language)
- That's me, I admit it!
(ominous music)
- This beautiful
panel could be yours!
- Well, back to Earth.
Same old, same old.
(wind blowing)
- Iron Eyes Cody.
- Oh no, it's Michael Landon,
what else could go wrong?
- Good thing my
slacks have memory.
- Englebert Humperdinck on
a very personal journey.
- Huh.
Well, I thought I
was supposed to film
a Teratin commercial out here.
- Did ancient astronauts
make dirt bunnies?
♪ Place in France where
the ladies wear no ♪
Oh.
- Another Buddhist monk.
- It's Coleman Francis mountain!
- Well, I've come to
where the flavor is
but nothing's happening!
♪ Place in France
where the ladies ♪
♪ Place is France ♪
I wish it'd stay in one key!
♪ There's a place in ♪
And I wish they'd finish
a phrase now and again!
♪ There's a place in France
where the ladies wear no pants ♪
♪ Hey bring it down now ♪
♪ Talkin' about that France ha ♪
♪ Where the ladies ain't
wearin' no knickers at all ♪
Hey!
- Well, who wants cake?
- [Crowd] I do!
- Oh man, if Pauly
Shore is in this.
- Yes, teens love their
cake pool parties.
(crowd murmuring)
- That's not really a
good Chippendale outfit.
- They're so excited they can
barely talk to each other.
- Look, why don't I slice
some and you can all
come back in about 10
minutes and I'll be ready.
(crowd laughing)
- It's Scott Baio class!
- Get your red-hot franks here!
- Squish, squish,
squish, squish.
- Oh, mama, wouldn't
Chuck like to give you
his red-hot frank right now.
- From what I hear,
Chucky, it ain't so hot.
- He's got affidavits!
- She undercut the subtle
nuance of my wiener joke!
(girl screaming)
(splashing)
- There!
I think I've taught you not
to rebuff my wiener innuendos!
(splashing)
- Mercifully, the wiener
debate ended peacefully,
but it could've
gone another way.
- She really opened up the
party, now it's fun, whee!
- Hey, Stoker, Murphy, Gubba!
- [All] Whoo!
- Whole movies are more
tightly edited than this!
- He's never far
from his trusty van.
- Hi, Billy.
- God, you're fatter than Mom.
- How about a swim?
- In a minute, I feel
kinda lazy right now.
- Oh, thank you for saying
that, that was so sweet!
- Well, at least he
dressed up for the party.
- Should we ask what
the bruises are from?
- Billy, Billy, watch me dive!
Billy, Billy, I'm
gonna dive in the pool,
watch, watch, watch, watch!
- We're goin' home, the
movie isn't fun anymore!
- Hey, I can go under the
water and count to five, whee!
Hey Billy, Billy,
hey Billy, Billy!
- I am so baked.
- Yes, it's a Manson
family reunion!
- I hear something, oh.
- Oh man, those
brownies must be loaded.
- It's Rover from the Prisoner!
(Crow gasping)
Smaller.
- Now, I myself have never
been a natural frolicker.
- No.
- No, not very.
- Come on, hey, leave me
alone, I'm not kiddin'!
- So, what, is the alien
hiding at the end of the pool?
- Just eat your spare ribs
in the pool, that's fine.
- Bike rack!
- Ooh!
- Ow!
- I wonder why no
one wants any cake.
- Cindy, you need to
get an eating disorder,
guys like anorexic girls!
- I'll take a bite.
- Some birthday.
Outside of you, Kathy, I don't
think anyone would've come
if it weren't for the pool.
- Don't be silly, Franny,
you've got lots of friends!
- Yeah, as long as I
don't run outta pools.
- Well, how about all
the gay men who like you?
- Um, I'm gonna go change.
Will you tell Billy
if he gets up?
- Well, she certainly
is a sparkling hostess.
- Yes, non-skinny women
are inherently unhappy.
- [Radio] The leading spokesmen
for the dissident army
said it would have
nuclear capability...
- Is there anything on the news
about the dissonant army thing?
- [Radio] While France today
exploded its 28th atom bomb.
- They tell me cake is bad
for me, what about radiation?
- Oh, you're fun.
- Have you seen Kathy?
- She went inside
to get changed.
- Well, I'd stay longer
but you're real fat.
- Personally, I can never
get enough sheet cake.
- [Radio] You couldn't hear
the darn thing except...
(dance music)
- Hey, it's the horse kid!
- Sometimes I worry
I'm not shallow enough!
- Boy, he's popular.
- I'm gonna burn some
cigarettes in her dad's carpet.
- You leave the movie
for the Parade of Homes?
- I tried to see them...
- Yeah, he's lured by the
siren song of 70s hits.
- Ooh, well, look at that, huh?
A shapeless mass.
Boy, you can really see how
he's so dark and not ordinary.
- A teen at a teen party,
what could be darker?
- Yeah.
- Guys I'm back from the rumpus
room, everything checks out.
- Have you seen Kathy?
- No, I haven't seen her.
- Hey, how are things
in the Blue Lagoon?
- I guess I'll check
out the hat collection.
- Hey, I'm in here!
- There's a dozen naked
teenage girls in there,
that's what happens
at these teen parties.
It's true!
- Anyone seen the director?
Just lookin' for
a light out here.
- No one wants to eat cake
and he can't find Kathy,
now the movie is really
starting to find its purpose!
- (gasping) Kathy's jockstrap!
(Kathy yelping)
- And Elway takes him down!
- Don't even pretend, Eddie!
(both struggling)
- Super Eddie Deezen!
A Microsoft meeting
goes horrible wrong!
- Illegal use of a Deezen!
- Whoa.
- Come on, you bastards!
- Oh, foot fault!
- Billy don't!
- Be a hero!
- He wants to fight.
- [Froggy] He wants to
get his head broken!
- Billy don't.
- Be a hero.
- Please, nothing happened,
please, Billy, for me?
Leave him alone!
(upbeat music)
- I was thinking that Gilbert...
(rumbling)
(all yelping)
- Oh, what's goin' on!
- I don't know!
Cambot, give me
rocket number nine!
(babies crying)
Man, we've hit a
field of star babies
and one of 'em's got the ship!
- Wow, he's upset, he
must need changing!
- I thought I smelled something!
- All right, here's
the plan, man.
You gotta get out there and
change that baby's diaper.
I'll walk you through
the procedure from here.
- [Tom Servo] Okay, we're
on it, Mike, let's move!
- Go, go, go!
- Go, go, go, go, go!
- Come on, out, out, out!
- Go, go, go, go!
- Good thing I hung on to this.
- [Tom Servo] Thank you!
(babies crying)
- Ugh, boy, geez, it
really stinks out here!
Well, hello, little baby!
Oh, baby needs
changing, doesn't he?
- Crow, snap out of it, man,
you cannot get
personally involved!
- [Tom Servo] Okay, Mike,
we've located the diaper tabs,
we're pulling the diaper off.
- Servo, wait!
Do you have the clean diaper
in your hand, ready to go?
- [Tom Servo] Oh, phew,
yeah, thanks, Mike!
Okay, the clean diaper
is at the ready,
Crow is pulling the
dirty diaper away!
(beeping)
- [Crow] Roger, tearing tabs
and taking off dirty diaper.
(Tom Servo and Crow gagging)
- Oh geez, oh no!
Nelson, we've got a problem!
The diaper leaked, it went
all the way up his back, ugh!
- Okay, okay, we'll
get you through this!
Failure is not an option!
Now slip the clean
diaper under his bottom!
- [Crow] What about
the baby wipes, Mike?
We've gotta clean him up!
- Okay, fine, but hurry up!
(Tom Servo and Crow coughing)
- [Crow] There, done and done!
- All right now, seal him
up and get outta there!
- [Tom Serv] There, star
baby is diapered, Mike!
- [Crow] What should we do
with the dirty diaper, Mike?
- Uh, I don't know, put
it on a shelf somewhere.
(alarm blaring)
Oh boy, we got movie
sign, let's move, men!
(whirring and clanking)
- Good job, Tom.
- You could've
waited for us, Mike!
- Well, I just had
to get in here.
- Is a cat layin' on
the organ or somethin'?
- Oh great, he lives
next to Alan Parsons.
- I'm not Adam Rourke!
(engine revving)
- Powered by a
20-horse Evinrude,
this Dodge Charger really...
♪ Love the one you're with ♪
♪ Do do do do do do ♪
(Tom Servo humming
wedding march)
- I don't know, schlemiel,
schlimazel, whatever.
- Anybody?
I climbed up here on the
cliff and I can't get down,
can you call somebody?
(eerie music)
- I got my ankle caught between
two rocks, I'm pretty stuck!
- Hello?
Anybody?
- I had the most marvelous time!
- I'll bet.
- He's overlooking
something, isn't he?
(tense music)
- Dennis Cole!
- His horn is caught in
some kind of bebop rhythm.
- Hey, Froggy!
- Keep it down!
- Just let me Deezen by ya!
- Billy's so good,
he'll just wait
up there until you call him.
♪ I am the lizard king ♪
(whooshing)
(booming)
- Sorry, had it on high!
- So how many cars
did he blow up?
- Wow, must have the
wrong size air filter!
- Oh Jesus!
- That was Cochise's Charger?
- That could've killed, it
could've killed all of us!
- We'd better get in the house.
- I'll call the police!
- The loss of any Dodge
Charger is an awful thing.
- Yeah, they thought
the spent plutonium rods
would be fine in the trunk!
- Ungar, Jeep, do you hear me?
- Great.
- Dumb cop and dumb cop.
They're dumb cops.
- Great, another Larry
Storch wannabe here.
(police radio chattering)
- And how are we doing this
morning, information desk?
Good.
- What beats me is how
you can swallow down
a whole hot tamale first
thing in the morning.
- I just feel like you might
not be ready for some football.
- You know what the lining of
your stomach must look like?
- Well it's pink and it secretes
a layer of protective
mucus that...
- Hold it, give me a bite!
- He's eating his own hand!
- Are you saying I
have an oral fixation?
- Jeep, Ungar, get in here!
- Chief Hummer, what?
- Nice of you to show up.
- (burping) You're welcome.
- Go over to the Walden
place and get a statement
from Franny Walden about that
car that blew up last night.
- Yeah, Whopper and
fries, you want anything?
- Can you handle that?
- You got it.
- Thank you.
- Oh, and hey, let's
be careful out there.
- Hey, they got the name
of your favorite band
on the side of the car there.
(all chuckling)
- These two were in True
West for many years.
- I think I see a big
jackrabbit back there,
I'm gonna focus on that.
- Interesting country,
the High Desert.
You'd think it was
pretty lifeless
but there's actually
a lot going on.
- You know, I'd like to
hear about it some time.
- Oh, well we've got time now!
- (chuckling) We should
probably get back to the movie.
- Oh, I suppose you're right.
♪ I shot the Meo but I
didn't shoot the other guy ♪
♪ Do do do do do ♪
- Is that Fish's wife typing?
- Denise!
- What're you doin',
typin' an album?
- Banging away as usual, sir.
- Oh, that's funny
every morning.
- This movie packs
the unflinching humor
of a Dik Browne panel.
- Hey look, he's got
electric paneling!
(typing)
- Well.
- Hm.
- Hey, the other car in town!
- I think they were going
for a Touch of Evil feel
but they got a touch
of somethin' else.
- The President stops
at the Westward Ho.
- Why did he take
the long way around?
- Let me see, oh,
that one's locked too,
I gotta go get a
hanger, gosh darn it.
- They've really captured the
stark beauty of this town.
(typing)
- And action!
Action!
- Come on in here.
- Ah, your copier down?
- What can I do for you, fella?
- I presume you've
heard of Tattletale.
- First you take your
feet off the desk,
second take the cigar
out of your mouth,
and third you stand up.
- Fourth you lick me.
- Who the hell are you?
- Well, let me show you
my Sam's Club membership.
- The man bearing this wallet
is crazy, do nothing he says!
- Excuse me, Mr.
Craig, I didn't know.
- I gotta go buy
Fish's laxative.
- Wow, who's the skirt?
(clattering)
- Won't you sit down, sir?
- I may sit down, I may not.
- Sheriff, where
are you currently
buying your office supplies?
- If I were to ask you if
anything unusual happened here
in the last 24 hours,
what would you say?
- I don't know, nothin' much.
- Except for the aliens landin'.
- I did get this call
about a car blowin' up
over at the old
Walden place, but...
- And Chuck can put
his fist in his mouth.
- I mean, that's just kid stuff,
you know, a prank,
kids foolin' around.
- I want a list of everyone up
at the house when it happened
and I want the town sealed off.
- What do you mean, Mr. Craig?
- I mean no newsflashes,
no news leaks,
no news period, unless
I say otherwise.
Understood?
- I understand, tan
man with wallet.
- Understood.
(futuristic music)
- Hey, it's new shirt day!
- Good thing my Zantigo
salary affords me
an endless supply of cars!
- Hey, Ford stands for Fix
or Repair Daily (laughing).
(Crow laughing)
- You don't look so bad, Billy.
(Tom Servo yelping)
- I feel so good,
I feel like an idiot
goin' to the doctor.
- What about the
lump on your chest?
- Oh, that's my nipple.
- I got it from
the Franklin Mint.
- My God, Billy, it's bigger!
- You know nothing
of my chest holes.
- Yeah, it seems like.
- Well, Dr. Mellon it is.
- Duh, I'm a dork (chuckling).
- Okay gun it, please, oh.
- Tonight on a very special
Roddy McDowall Hospital.
- Hey!
- Well, it's big but
not as big as mine.
- So you have a
doorbell on your chest.
- Hmm, I was in a monkey suit
then suddenly I
was in this movie.
- Oh, dear God, Mrs. Mither
was a long, long time ago.
- Can I get dressed
now, Dr. Mellon?
- Certainly Bright Eyes, oh.
- No, not yet.
- It is ape law.
- Come in the other room.
- Take off my clothes.
- Lie down, Billy.
- But don't rip the paper,
I'd like to save it.
- Well, I'm going in.
- Ding dong.
- Operation!
- Remove wrenched ankle.
- Does that hurt?
- No, doctor.
- What if I stomp up
and down on your chest?
- Well, it looks as if you
have an impacted wood tick.
- Frankly, Billy, I'm
baffled and grossed out.
- Ding dong.
Ding dong.
- That?
- It appears to be growing into
a Wizard of Oz
commemorative plate.
(tapping)
- Uh, come in.
- Do you feel that?
- No.
- Well, medical science has done
everything possible, good-bye.
- Quite frankly...
- I don't know why
I took this role.
- Billy, I must
confess, I am puzzled.
That is quite close
to the surface,
what I would like to
do is try to remove it,
if that's all right with you.
- Sure, Doc, whatever you think.
- Okay.
- Let me grab a big
melon baller here
and really dig in there.
- Now, what I'm going to
do is give you a local
to anesthetize the
area, it won't hurt.
- Well, it will, I lied.
- And he delivers on his
promise to give him a local.
(eerie music)
- Oh, why did I do that, now
I have to fill it up again!
- Toodles!
- The hell, I've never
seen one of these!
- Good, got the nose hair
trimmers, the toe nail clippers.
- Oh, How Green Was My
Valley was a long time ago.
- I smoked many a great
doobie with this, yes.
- Now the makeup may have
to be patched after this
but there shouldn't
be any scarring.
- Ugh.
It's a St. Paul Winter
Carnival medallion.
- Oh!
- Hair shift!
- Now you be careful that
doesn't get infected, huh?
- Uh-huh.
- You okay, Billy?
- Sure, Doc patched
me up just fine.
- Oh, by the way, give me
a call in a couple of days
because I'm gonna run
that specimen over
to Springfield myself tonight
and I'll have the answer
in about 12 hours.
- Thanks, Doc.
- Yes, thank you.
- They're at the kiddie clinic.
- Would you mind cleaning
up the examining room?
- I was getting into my ape role
and I threw some crap around.
- Hm, I've gotta see
if Beyond the Valley
of the Planet of
the Apes is a go.
Yeah, Mike?
Oh, glad I caught you.
At lunch, huh?
- (chuckling)
Surprised you notice
something like lunch time.
How are you, Doc?
Long time, no see.
- Here, do somethin' with that.
- Listen, Mike, I want
you to do me a favor.
- Sure, Doc, shoot.
- I would like to bring a
specimen over tonight and...
- No!
- No, after hours, I'm afraid
it will be around midnight.
Would you wait?
- I'll be waiting
in my peignoir.
- It's that important?
- It could be.
- But probably isn't.
- I'll get there
as soon as I can
but I am afraid it
will be after midnight.
- I will be letting
it all hang down.
- Thank you.
All right, good-bye.
- Wait, I'm a
Lenscrafter technician,
what does he want with me?
- Again, true to his word,
he delivers the specimen.
- Mm-hmm, this
movie boldly states
what it's gonna do and does it!
- Make sure there's a pin spot
on Mr. McDowall's right ear.
- This is one of my
greatest specimens
- I almost hate to give it away.
- Man, he's just
beggin' to be abducted!
(eerie music)
- It's George Jones
as a Walmart greeter!
- All righty then!
- Don't do that.
- Sorry.
- Roddy McDowall is Silkwood.
- Wow, he's really over
driving his headlights!
(whooshing)
- Oh no, his car
turned into a sedan
and crashed and exploded!
- We show you this scene
to represent what
would've happened.
(crashing)
- So this is how
Roddy McDowall died?
- He's not dead.
- Oh.
- Well, at least he was
wearing his seatbelt!
(warbling)
- I believe this is Mannix,
if I'm not mistaken.
(alien speaking alien language)
- Ants are up?
- I need another neck rub!
(alien speaking alien language)
- Shut up, green boy.
(aliens speaking alien language)
- I can't believe
you said that to me!
(alien speaking alien language)
- Meow!
(beeping)
- He has a silver
cactus oven mitt.
- Do you know anything that
will shrink the swelling?
- We used to have one
of these in school!
- Isn't that doorknob
abnormally high?
- What're you
doing here so late?
- I'm calibrating
my interferometer.
- Yeah, you go
ahead and do that.
- I've got to find
out what time it is!
- He could play
Gertrude Stein so easy!
- Uh, Peggy, would you look
up some numbers for me?
- Two and nine.
- First see if Dr.
Mellon's at home.
- Rap him for a hollow sound.
- And if he's not, try
the sheriff's office.
- Michael Caine's puffy sister.
- Is this your coin?
- This movie is comprised
strictly of second unit footage.
- Hey, we're still havin'
trouble with our copier.
- This forced
perspective is so phony,
he's not really
that big, you know.
- We may just have
ourselves a mad bomber here.
- I'm not mad, I'm disappointed!
- Bad movies have
taught us that sheriffs
hold onto their belts a lot.
- What do you think?
- You should call the
lab in Springfield,
tell them we found what's
left of Dr. Mellon.
- Uh, which Springfield?
There's one in every state.
- Go ahead you two.
- They present a formidable
law enforcement team, huh?
- I want a list of
everybody that's seen
the doctor in the last 24 hours.
- Should I close off
the island, Steve?
- Let's get down
to work, sheriff,
we're runnin' out of time.
- What about the rights
of that little girl?
(gentle music)
- (laughing) Hey, your
sister wants her shirt back!
- I figured out
this kind of shirt,
no complicated
buttons to deal with!
- Ow, it hurts to get in my
van with these tight jeans.
- I think we're supposed to
like him because he has a van.
- You know, every time I
come close to not hating him,
I see those feet on
the side of the van.
- They got that
antenna to get some
Elvin Bishop and
Marshall Tucker music.
- Thrill as the police
forget something.
- Oh, oh, okay, break the
stunt, it didn't work.
- He'd make a
pretty Sharon Glass.
- He's his own airbag.
- (sighing) Billy, Billy, Billy.
- Man, forgot what
I was gonna say,
it was somethin' good, too!
- You're gettin' to be a
real Dillinger, ain't ya boy?
- Must not react.
- Made a call into your place.
- Uh, I can't hear your
through the window!
I see your lips moving...
- Where do you
think you're going?
- Nothing.
- Man, I just remembered
what I was gonna say!
- Anything you say can be used
to get you ready
for some football!
- I know where you're goin'.
- Boy camel-toe!
(Mike and Tom Servo groaning)
(upbeat music)
- Allen Fawcett!
- [Sheriff] What
do you know about
Chuck's car being blown up.
- Chuck's carbon doughnuts?
- All I know is what I heard
when Kathy picked
me up this morning.
- Where'd you go?
- To Dr. Mellon's.
I had this sore on my
chest and Kathy thought
I should let the
doctor look at it.
I don't like going
to doctors but...
- But it was Roddy
McDowall, he made it fun!
- Do you mind showing us?
- Oh, it's a Calvin Klein ad.
- Of course not.
- He's got a creamy center!
- Good God!
- Hey, you're not trip
to Hollywood either!
- What's the matter?
- Nothin'.
- I'm not ready for
football anymore.
- Thanks for comin' in.
- But we've already
cast the part.
- You need a ride back, Billy?
- No thanks, Sheriff,
I can make it.
- Man, I could eat him.
Tear off the wrapper, pop him
in the microwave, one bite.
- Everything seen and heard
in this room stays
here, understood?
- Even the file cabinets?
- Understood?
- Absolutely.
I ain't never seen
nothin' like that.
- And I've been to a
county seat and everything!
- [Ungar] What was it?
- That's just what
I'm gonna go find out.
- Glad you could
help, whoever you are.
- Just love these little
Mom and Pop sheriff outfits.
(ominous music)
- Oh no, another dead dog,
I gotta remember
to crack a window!
- D'oh!
- I should get my
nose sharpened.
- Oh, they're showin' that
he's a misunderstood rebel
because he doesn't
have a ride home.
- Are you a woman?
- It's a training microscope!
- Now merge carefully
with the flagellum.
- Then on the
delicate cycle here.
- No, you're right, this
data proves I'm a woman!
- Little bit of that, some
of that there, there we go.
- They're looking at those old,
weird, naked Daguerreotypes.
- So, what do you like?
Country or light rock, maybe?
- I want you to know how
much this has meant to me,
whatever your name is.
- Let's do it tomorrow, I've
got a tanning appointment.
- A self-administered eye exam!
- Hi, sir, bye, sir.
- Well, I've given
it every test I know,
it's, it's the oddest thing.
- The oddest thing what?
- The material is nothing
that comes of this Earth.
There were some
traces of burnt flesh
but the mass of it is inorganic.
- You sure of that?
- No, I'm really only
a dental hygienist.
- Absolutely.
And I'll tell you
something else,
if you won't think I'm crazy.
- I've got grasshoppers
taped to my back.
- Whatever it is, it's growing.
- You're not crazy.
Have you found
anything to destroy it?
- Oh my Lord, heavens no, dear!
No, darling.
- Well, good-bye,
Mrs. Joe Don Baker.
- Thanks, Mike.
- Hope the sex change
operation goes all right.
- And my hair is perfect.
- Emergency Alert One.
- Tonight on COPS.
- You know, I saw a COPS
once where they pulled
this skinny guy out
from under a couch.
- No!
- You ever see that?
- This sucks, I was
supposed to headline!
- What now?
- I can use a Coke!
- I think there are other
issues between these two.
- Oh man.
(clanking)
- Who's the well-lit
person in back there?
- Say, I got my leg stuck in
a mole hole over here, um...
- David Bowie!
- Cool!
(tense music)
- Now he knows
how to use a Coke!
♪ I'd like to teach the world
to get ready for some football ♪
- Give me some of that.
(Crow laughing goofily)
- Come on, stop using my Coke!
- I gotta use the john.
- Ah, test audiences
responded well
to bulbous crackers
using the john.
- This is like Porky's
without the charm.
- Oh good, we get to see
him unfurl his pants.
- Aw damn, there's only six
rolls of toilet paper left!
- All right, watch
out, thunderbucket,
you're about to meet
your greatest challenge.
- Eh!
- Somebody stop me!
(whooshing)
(booming)
- Can I get a plunger?
- Ah!
- Ew, that smell!
- Wait, save the nut goodies!
- Save the pine
tree air fresheners!
- Save the dirty trucker tapes!
(whooshing)
(booming)
- I'm thinkin' this
and Roddy McDowall
ate up about 90% of
the film's budget.
- I thought it was just one
gas station but it's four!
(booming)
- Well, they needed
to remodel anyway.
(booming)
- Mother!
(wooshing)
♪ If I built a fortress
around your heart ♪
- Haven't we been
through enough?
- Do you have to invite your
van every time we do this?
I can hear it breathing!
- Now, what do they need to grab
from the cooler during the act?
- Was that it?
Oh well, good try.
- Look how different
it all looks, Billy.
- It's my hands and stuff.
- Billy, you asleep?
- No, of course not.
I heard every word you said.
- Oh, then what did I say then?
- How different it
all looks, Billy.
- God, I hope they forgot
to set the parking brake.
- Whatever that means.
- Absolutely,
positively revolting!
- Ah, musty army blanket
and a pair of dirty sneakers
always gets you in the mood, eh?
(all groaning)
- Oh, too close, too close!
- Ugh.
- He's sucking the snake
venom out of some place.
- Ugh.
- Man, I agree with Abby,
people should just cuddle.
- Oof, oof!
- Ugh!
- What is that?
- Can you show that?
- Ugh!
(shuddering)
Ugh, Robert Ginty
was a better kisser!
- This movie means
two things to me,
sheet cake and back fat!
- If you could
taste what I hear.
- It's pretty waxy in
there today, Billy.
- Ugh!
- I just hope she gets
combat pay for this.
(farting)
- Oh well, I'll finish in town.
- Is that something you
should have checked out?
I mean, do you think
it's physical or mental?
Oh, well.
- Well, I gotta get
back to my regiment.
- Shouldn't the lockbox
be on the house?
- It's a hand grenade necklace.
- Hmm, from the Sarah
Coventry Collection.
- Now pull the pin and run!
- Oh, Billy, between you and
the motor oil and your BO
and the scabby hole in your
chest, I just love you!
(ominous music)
- His nipples look
like jean rivets!
- Ah, just when I thought he
couldn't be less appealing.
- Well, that fired him up!
(Kathy screaming)
- Why didn't she do that
when she was kissing him?
- Oh, that dumb!
- So they're just off county
road C goin' at it, huh?
(whirring and clanking)
- Man, it's beautiful, isn't it?
- Absotively gorgeous!
I wonder what it is.
- I don't know.
- It's a black hole!
It's a black hole!
- Of course, you know, I
had a feeling about that.
- And we're being
sucked towards it
and the short explanation
is that we're all gonna die!
(Crow and Tom Servo sobbing)
- Oh, bitter irony,
I just read an article
by Stephen Hawking!
- Hold me, Crow, embrace me
in the moment of oblivion.
- Don't worry, Mike can help us,
he's kinda smart and his
arms work and everything!
- Yeah!
What're we panicking
for, huh? (laughing)
Mike can fix it!
- Yeah, he won't let us die,
he's frosty in the
clutch! (laughing)
- Oh, we are in deep trouble!
(Crow, Tom Servo,
and Gypsy screaming)
- Stow it, you two!
Mr. Gypsy, status report!
- Sir, the ship has been trapped
in the gravity well
of a black hole
and is presently plummeting
towards the singularity!
- Mr. Cambot, red alert!
Mr. Gypsy, you're with me!
Mr. Servo, you have the com.
All right, what we need
to do is realign...
- Uh, what's he doin'
with my toy phone?
- Uh, I don't know,
but don't bother him.
Sure, he's gone totally mental,
but look how poised
he is, how confident!
- You know, you're right,
and he has the subtle allure
of a woman in the full
flower of early middle age.
- All right!
I've realigned the Penrose
tubes and jettisoned a stream
of Einsteinium through
the Hawking converter,
thereby reversing the
Oppenheimer effect
and propelling us through
the Asimov space curtain.
Mr. Cambot, engage!
(whirring)
Mr. Gypsy, report.
- We've pulled free
of the singularity
and returned to
plummeting out of control
at an ever -ncreasing speed
towards some unknown doom!
- Oh!
- Excellent!
Now, Mr. Servo, Mr.
Crow, I'm responsible
for the lives of 148 crew
members aboard this ship,
144 of which we never see,
but sometimes I have
to get a little rough.
Yeah, that's the way
I like it, rough!
Because I never, ever, do
anything nice and easy!
♪ Rollin' rollin'
rollin' on the river ♪
- Back away slowly!
♪ I took a job in the city ♪
- Very slowly and run!
♪ Every night and day ♪
♪ Rollin' rollin'
rollin' on the river ♪
(upbeat music)
- Wow.
(Mike humming)
- Yes, we're making restitution
to all who had sex with Billy.
- Although not admitting
any wrongdoing,
we agree to compensate you
for having had sex with Billy.
- Oh, hold on, give me a
second to get crazy here!
- It's Kris Kringle
in retirement!
- Hello sir or ma'am, do you
need any law enforcement?
- Tony Craig!
- That would be a
good name for you!
- Of the wars, I'd say.
Well come in, come in.
- Oof, a mouse die in
your air conditioning?
- Not bad.
- Yeah, it's mediocre.
I figured for a bigger finish.
- Maybe General?
- I wet myself today, wanna see?
- No!
- Yeah.
- Oh, that old smuggler
will sneak up on ya.
- I bought the drapes too short
but I found a way
to deal with it.
- Oh, hello, have
you been helped?
- They offered me
an early retirement.
I accepted.
Hobson's Choice.
- You know, with Meryl Streep
and Kevin Klein and all?
- Sit down, sit down,
make yourself comfortable.
- Can I offer you some pajamas?
- So what's your problem?
Have a drink?
- How about a little
fabric softener for ya?
(Billy groaning)
- Ugh!
(whooshing)
(booming)
- Must've lost a quarter
in there sometime.
- Scenes cut from Roadhouse.
(Tom Servo groaning)
- Let's see what else peeves me.
Gonna get that woman who
asked me for two forms of ID!
- He insists on bringing
his leaf blower everywhere.
- Looks like he's scooping
insects with his baleen.
♪ Do do do do ♪
♪ Do do do do do do ♪
- Wow, he's being out
acted by a drainpipe.
- Filmed with husbands
and wives cam!
- An Occurrence at
Owl Creek Bridge
and the Destruction of Jared-Syn
through the portal of time.
(Crow imitating dog barking)
- Where the heck is
commercial office suppliers?
- Oh goody, my lucky spot!
- 22 to dispatch.
(country music)
♪ Gather round ♪
♪ Gather round
children get loud ♪
♪ You can be proud yeah ♪
♪ Be proud you're a rebel ♪
♪ 'Cause the South's
gonna do it again ♪
Today only, aliens golf free!
(Tom imitating alien warbling)
♪ Gather round ♪
♪ Gather round children ♪
♪ Get down ♪
♪ You can get down children ♪
♪ Get loud ♪
♪ You can get loud
and be proud ♪
♪ You can get proud yeah ♪
♪ Be proud you're a rebel ♪
♪ 'Cause the South's
gonna do it again ♪
- Boy, this has gotta be
the best buggy in town!
I can't wait 'til everybody
sees us drivin' around in this!
You know, I can't believe
them insurance guys
actually believed that
stupid story about lightning.
- Shut up, Froggy.
- You know, Eddie
looks like a meerkat.
- These cars always look
like they've got angry faces!
(Tom Servo growling)
- You know, I can't believe
them Springfield dudes
would actually believe
that story about lightning.
I mean, you gotta be
stupid to actually think...
- Froggy, shut up.
- Sure, Chuck, sure.
- Like before when you asked
me to shut up, sure, sure.
- Come on, just blow the car up!
- Eddie has a special car
seat his friend puts him in.
- Eddie's like a
puppy you just have to
keep hittin' with a
rolled up newspaper.
- Where?
- In town, I thought
I saw lightning!
- Would you knock it off
with that lightning crack?
- (chuckling) They are just
like Williams and Reed!
♪ Be loud ♪
- So Servo, exactly what is
the South going to do again?
- You know, different activities
that they have done in the past
that they'd like to
kind of do again.
(gasping) 45 speed limit?
A plane?
Wow, it's all going together!
(plane humming)
- This whole scene
was just an excuse
to play that great music!
- Now you got me thinking
about the South doin' again,
it's just the South, okay?
- Sorry, I was just askin'!
- Okay, just the spirit.
- Oh hey, look, look, look,
look, look, over there,
over there, over
there, over there,
look, look, look, look, look!
- So, he's observing
the speed limit I see.
- This is so Coleman
Francis right now.
- Now he's takin' Eddie
to the vet to get fixed.
♪ Get down ♪
Are you takin' me
to the big place?
- Yes, Eddie, you'll
like it at the big place.
- I know.
♪ Be loud and be proud ♪
- On Cherokee Jack.
- That's Eddie Deezen down
there, let's take him out!
- Uh, we still on
the same movie?
Hello?
- Whoa, this was so great when
it was at the Omnitheater.
- Look, a raccoon!
(plane humming)
- This must be a hot
one, let's go get him!
- Sure, hell, but who are we
and what're we
doing in this film
and why was Eddie
Deezen waving at us?
- Tonight on a very
special Simon and Simon.
- All I'll say is it's
just Southern pride, Mike,
there's no specific act
they're gonna do again.
- I mean, that's fine, lay off.
♪ One tin soldier rides away ♪
- Ron Howard decides to
take out Brother Clint.
- There, has to be on
just right for this.
- Could Leonard Maltin be wrong
and this isn't worth
two and a half stars?
(plane humming)
(whooshing)
- That could be a
federal offense.
- Grr, gonna make that
kid button his shirt
if it's the last thing I do!
- I knew I forgot something!
- Well, Reno gave us the
go ahead, let's do it!
(tense music)
(gun firing)
- That's probably someone
who did somethin',
well, let's shoot 'em!
- Ooh, looked like Stuart
Copeland for a moment.
- So, I mean, we shouldn't
worry about the South?
- Don't, just, lay
off the South, okay?
It's not real, it's
just the feeling!
- Okay.
- So there's a label maker
on top of the laserblaster.
- You know, Mike, this
film was run through
a highly technical process
called tension extraction
before it was released
to the theaters.
- I got him!
- You nailed it!
- Or not, I couldn't be sure!
- Yeah!
- Nipple check, yep,
nipples in tact.
- Make sure when
you do the scene
you don't direct any
of this at the camera.
- Eegah!
- [Pilot] The son of
a bitch is still up!
- Oh yeah!
- I can't get this
poster tube off my arm!
- Hello, Grand Rapids, are
you ready to rock and roll?
- Now, we're just spraying
paraquat, citizen,
go about your business.
♪ Dun dun dun dun ♪
- Red Zone Cuba III: The
Destruction of Cherokee Jack.
- Hey, where'd they go?
Whoa!
- Oh, that's a good way
to tear your rotator cuff.
- Will you please blow up?
This scene is dragging!
(whooshing)
(booming)
- There!
- There we go.
- Thank you, thank you very
much, Indianapolis, we love you!
- Wh, ow, oh, that did it.
- JD Power and Associates
rank these guys
the most loathsome
in their class.
- This is fine right here,
I don't wanna get any
close to Eddie Deezen.
- Mm-mm.
Come on, Chuck, talk to me!
Every time we go to a
wedding, we get in a fight!
- Won't be long now!
- I get to pet the llama, right?
(ominous music)
- Yes, it's the brand-new
Weed Whipper Two.
- Honey, isn't that
the Johnson boy?
What's he doing in our backyard?
- So, Servo, I mean...
- Oh, just lay off!
You'll see, when the
South does rise again,
I'll be laughin', me, me!
- Okay, all right, all right!
Man.
Right, so how's this
guy undo his fly
when he has to go
to the bathroom?
♪ Dun dun dun dun do do
do do do do do do hoo ♪
- Okay, get your butt off
the window now, Eddie.
- Apparently Chuck pinned Eddie.
- Is this one of those movies
based on a Jane Austen novel?
- Hey, Chuck, who's the creep?
(dramatic music)
- Hey, creep, you want a lift?
I say we give this
bum a real treat,
a ride he'll never forget!
- Yeah!
- Yes, do it!
- Shoot him, take him out!
- Shoot!
- Aah, I'm certain whatever's
on his arm is
incredibly perilous!
(booming)
- Ooh!
- We'll never know where
they were going now.
- Well, that was rough goin',
I think the worst is over,
I'll just pull over here.
- Hey Eddie, hey Chuck,
I like the flames you
painted on your, oh!
- Okay, no problem,
got it under control,
just pump the brakes
gently, there we go!
- Hmm, temperature
gauge is running hot,
wonder what that, oh, yeah.
- Mind if I crack
a window, Eddie?
- Not to worry, a Nick
Stick came with the car.
- There goes a very
gifted shop student!
- Shame!
♪ Something touched
me deep inside the day
Eddie Deezen died ♪
(upbeat music)
- I gotta start monitoring
the people I have sex with.
- Cheryl Ladd in
A Soldier's Story.
- You'll get your drinking
badge with this one.
- Come here often?
Aren't these places phony?
(whirring)
- Billy must be somewhere close.
- Don't you ever say
(mumbling) to me again!
- Billy!
- Don't be a hero!
- Hi, honey, I'm a cop now.
- Was Billy in that car?
Come on, let's go.
(Tom Servo imitating guitar)
♪ Goin' home ♪
- Kids, ugh.
Wait, somethin' wrong
with the whammy bar.
There we go.
♪ My baby ♪
(Tom Servo imitating guitar)
- Hey, Steve, Steve,
the film crew!
- Oh!
- Yeah, my first time with Bill
Rosemann in that car there.
(aliens speaking alien language)
- It's a Miss Hathaway alien!
- Sure, throw that
up in my face!
- I see him grinnin'.
- Well, I'm not hitchhikin'
but if you wanna
give me a ride, okay!
- We're goin' to Iowa
City to see the Dead!
- We saw Anthrax last night,
we got hammered and puked.
- You know, I should
tell you about
my ass, gas, or grass policy.
- Well, there I was,
30,000 feet straight up!
Field of frozen yo-yos
and the string broke!
I didn't falter, I just kept
on goin' me, and I knew,
I knew Nirvana was
straight around the corner.
- Nirvana.
- I turned the corner, ran
smack into Betty Cochran,
she was runnin' across
the sky yellin',
"You never outgrow
your need for milk!"
- I miss Eddie Deezen.
- I looked at her, I said,
"Baby, you're somethin' else."
- Then I discovered Poco.
- [Man] All right, man,
you know what I mean?
- He's like a lucid
Dennis Hopper.
- Whatchu doin'?
How'd you get out here?
There ain't nothin' but
rattlesnakes and turtles.
- You may or may
not believe this,
but I grow my own Mary Jane!
Cousin of yours, Mike?
- What the?
- Hm?
- There's just a sign
that says Star Wars?
- Reminding one of
the movie Star Wars.
- I hadn't finished
reading that!
- Far out!
- Because hippies are stoned.
- Ah-ha.
- Oh, camera rig on
the ride of the van.
(car horn blaring)
- Hey, you got a
camera rig on your car!
(ominous music)
- This guy breasts
the tape in front of
Steven Alaimo for loathsomeness.
- All righty then!
- You kill me, my whole commune
will hunt you down, I swear!
(man screaming)
(whooshing)
- You are wrong, mariajuana
breath (giggling)!
♪ Do do do do do ♪
- I bet the heater's
stuck on full blast, too.
- So the aliens have
been sent to Earth
to acquire righteous vans.
- Meanwhile, on a similar
road, traffic moves freely!
- So I wonder what
the flaw was that kept
Leonard Maltin from giving
this the full three stars.
- But alien problems do not
exist here at Bear Path,
a planned golf community.
- Fore!
(whooshing)
(booming)
- My mailbox of values!
- Oh look, everyone was sending
a sheet of paper
to everyone else.
- Now, why did they call
this movie Laserblast?
(booming)
- Oh, it's raining porn!
Hallelujah!
- So what East coast Southern
California town is this?
- Leave the Bronx, you are
ordered to leave the Bronx.
- Mark Hamill in Falling Down.
- Ecuadorian bat boy
found alive in cave!
- Where am I?
Isn't there an information
booth around here?
(Mike laughing goofily)
- Oh, someone's
got a full diaper.
- Oh, tai chi in the
morning is so great.
- Will you help me carry this?
It's really heavy!
- Er, er, er, come on, our
reservations are at eight!
(whirring)
- Neil Diamond,
Hot August Nights.
- Don't ever make
fun of my ass again!
♪ What would you do if
I sang out of tune ♪
- Killed by vapor action.
- Really sorry about the
whole South thing, Mike,
you have a valid point.
- No, that's all
right, it's all right.
- Nuts, my thing ran
out, got a battery?
- My ovipositor's sore.
- Wow, she makes Laraine
Newman look Rubenesque!
- So, ever make it with
a mid-level bureaucrat?
- Fashion from Sears.
- Wait, my belt's out the door!
- No more nights
on musty blankets.
I'll really miss
your open shirts.
We'll play REO Speedwagon
at your funeral, Billy.
- This is really where he
hits his stride as an actor.
- I guess I should know
what it is that the South
would do again before I
jump on the bandwagon.
- Yeah, that's true.
- Would you just let that die?
- Okay, let's look
in Maltin's book.
Uh, he gives this
two-and-a-half stars.
Ooh, My Favorite Year barely
edges it out with three stars.
- Huh.
- Oh, look here,
Hannah and her Sisters
is superior only by one star.
- Oh, wow.
- Oh great, now a tire fire
starts just off camera!
(Tom coughing)
- Okay.
Oh, hey, Leonard
Maltin gave the same
two-and-a-half stars to
My Dinner with Andre.
- Name of the Rose?
This is a better film
than Name of the Rose,
it only got two stars!
- Being There, two stars.
- Uh, Lucas Tanner,
the movie was directed
by Richard Donner.
I just thought I'd
point that out.
- Oh, good.
- Lemme see here.
- You mean, you mean to
tell me that Ron Masak
and Eddie Deezen get
billing over Roddy McDowall?
- Look Mike, Birdman of
Alcatraz, three stars,
marginally better
than Laserblast.
- They spelled Roddy
McDowall's name wrong!
- What else you got?
- Oh, here we go, Full
Metal Jacket, three stars.
- Hm?
- It's a shame, isn't it?
- Oh, hey, Seven
Samurai, two stars.
- What?
- I'm kidding, I'm kidding.
- Oh.
- I hope so.
- According to this,
A Fish Called Wanda
was as good a film
as Laserblast.
- D'oh!
- Broadcast News,
Witness, three stars,
barely superior to Laserblast.
- Mm-hm.
- Same for Diner.
- Yeah.
Oh, here we go, this
was a better movie
than Indiana Jones and
the Temple of Doom.
Two stars!
- Well, that's possible.
- And the same caliber
as Last Crusade,
two-and-a-half stars!
- And, uh, and yet, Blame It
On the Bellboy, four stars!
- Where?
- What?
- No, I'm kidding, I'm kidding.
- Oh, you, you, jeez.
- So, Kim Milford's greasy,
pop-eyed performance
was every bit as good
as F. Murray Abraham's
tortured performance
as Salieri in Amadeus.
- According to Leonard
Maltin, yes, Mike.
- Baghdad Cafe,
brilliant subtle comedy,
no better than Laserblast.
- Here's where it gets hard,
Harry and the Hendersons is
every bit as good as Laserblast.
- Carson McCullers' classic
the Heart is a Lonely Hunter,
no better than Laserblast.
- No, no...
- Ah, ah, ah,
John Schlesinger's Oscar-winning
thriller Marathon Man
on par with Laserblast,
two-and-a-half stars.
- Right, so Laurence
Olivier's chilling performance
as Szell, the White Angel,
no better than the butt-faced
sheriff in Laserblast.
- Again, according to
Leonard Maltin, yes, Mike.
- Okay.
- Ah, look here, look here,
Outlaw Josey Wales and
Unforgiven, Oscar-winners,
quintessential Westerns,
Eastwood at his finest.
However, I think you know
where we're headed
with this, Mike.
- Uh, yeah, yeah.
- [Tom Servo And Mike]
Same as Laserblast.
- Two-and-a-half stars.
- Oh, here we go,
here's a couple more.
Sophie's Choice.
- Uh huh.
- Uh, here's one, Willy Wonka
and the Chocolate Factory.
- No!
- The Great Santini.
- Oh, I can't believe that!
- All two-and-a-half stars.
- Two-and-a-half stars.
- The same quality.
- Also known as Ace, by the way.
- Yes, Ace.
- Peers to Laserblast.
(dramatic music)
(whirring and clanking)
- Wow.
- See that?
- Hey, here we are at
the edge of the universe!
- Well, not quite, Mike,
there's just a little
bit more to go here.
- Oh, yeah, you're right.
(thudding)
- Ah, there, the
edge of the universe!
- Yep, and I tell ya, Mike,
it's everything I
could've hoped for.
For example, all knowledge
is clear to me now!
- Yeah, you know, and
all wisdom and beauty
fill me an abundant light
and all the eternal truths
of the cosmos are available
with a minimum of effort!
- Well, hey, there's God!
Oh, maybe not.
- Oh.
- Hey guys, what's up?
- Hey!
- Oh, we're just at the
edge of the universe.
- Oh, so that's it!
No wonder I've
suddenly become aware
that I can leave my corporeal
body and become pure energy!
Or pure thought or reason or
pure any number of things!
- Cool!
- Here, let's see.
(Crow grunting)
(whooshing)
- Wow, cool!
Let's do it, Mike!
(Tom Servo grunting)
(whooshing)
- [Crow] Just let
it happen, Mike.
- Okay, gotcha.
- [Tom Servo] Come on.
Yeah, there you see?
- [Mike] Wow,
Servo, what are you?
- [Tom Servo] I think
I am pure energy!
- [Crow] Hey, I'm pure energy!
- [Tom Servo] Ah, you're nothin'
but pure canola oil, you!
- [Crow] Oh yeah, Mr. Pure
Country, Mr. Pure Gin,
Mr. Pure Chewing Satisfaction!
- [Tom Servo] Want
a piece of me?
- [Mike] Hey, guys,
come on, come on,
spread out now, come on.
All that matters is that
we're pure and eternal.
- [Tom Servo] Yeah.
- Oh, hello?
- [Mike] Oh, hey, Gypsy, hey!
Why don't you drop
you temporal being
and become pure
love or somethin'
and then we'll all go play
on the edge of the universe!
- Yeah!
- Yay, woo-hoo!
- I don't know.
- Oh, come on, it'll be fun!
- Come on, Gypsy,
it's really fun,
don't be afraid!
- [Tom Servo] It's so fun
to not have body, come on!
- I'm not sure it's just
that, oh, oh, oh my stars!
(all chuckling)
- [Tom Servo] I hope
I'm ready for this!
I may only be 99 and 44 one
hundredths percent pure!
- [Mike] Well, that's
probably good enough.
- Yeah!
- Let's go!
- [Mike] Oh, hey, Cambot,
Magic Voice, join us!
- [Gypsy] Yeah, come on!
(all laughing)
- [Crow] Oh, it's
great out here!
- [Tom Servo] It's
great, it's cold,
and I don't care,
I'm pure energy!
(heavy breathing)
(clanking)
(chair scraping)
(shattering)
(ethereal moaning)
- (gasping) Another
chance to do it right!
Isn't this wonderful, baby?
- [Dr. Forrester] Oh, poopy!
(calm music)
- Far out!